{
    "lvl2" :[
        {
            "question": "What do you type to start a new line in a string?",
            "answer": "\n",
            "id": 1   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of loop iterates or repeats a set amount of times?",
            "answer": "if",
            "id": 2   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of loop iterates or repeates while a condition is stays true",
            "answer": "while",
            "id": 3   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of loop iterates or repeates and performs at least once while a condition stays true?",
            "answer": "do-while",
            "id": 4   
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you type to tab in the middle of a string",
            "answer": "\t",
            "id": 5   
        },
        {
            "question": "Which variable uses whole numbers?",
            "answer": "int",
            "id": 6   
        },
        {
            "question": "Which variable allows uses of  decimal numbers?",
            "answer": "float",
            "id": 7   
        },
        {
            "question": "Which variable allows a single character? ",
            "answer": "char",
            "id": 8   
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill in the blank: for(x = 0; x < 10; ___)",
            "answer": "x++",
            "id": 9   
        },
        {
            "question": "fill in the blank for the loop to iterate 12 times: for(i = 0; i < __; i++)",
            "answer": "12",
            "id": 10   
        }
    ]
}